A Guide to the Executive Papers of Governor E. Lee Trinkle, 1919-1929 [bulk 1922-1926]
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Extraditions, Pardons, and Prison Affairs, 1922-1926., Extent: 10.35 cu. ft. (23 boxes). (Box Boxes 79-101)
  - Subseries B. Pardons
    - Clement - Colvin (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Combs - Craig (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Creech - Curtis (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Dance - Dawson (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Dean - Devlin (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Dillard - Dobbs (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Dodson - Dyer (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Eanes - Ellyson (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Emory - Eye (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Faison - Flippo (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Flora - Fox (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Franklin - Fuller (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Gaardsmore - Gordon (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Graham - Guthrie (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Haden - Hall (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Hamilton - Harlow (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Harrell - Harrison (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Harrold - Haynes (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Headlee - Hermann (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Hicks - Hinton (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Hodnett - Horton (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - Hosier - Hoy (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Hudgins - Hylton (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Ingle - Janson (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Jarrell - Jett (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Johnson, A - J (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Johnson, L - W (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Jones, A - J (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Jones, M - W (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Joo - Joyner (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - Kates - Koons (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Lafayette - Layne (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Lee - Lewis (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Ligg - Lynn (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - McCargo - McNeal (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Maas - Martin (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Mason - Mazell (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Meadows - Mitchell (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Moore - Motley (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Mullins - Myers (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Nash - Nunnally (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Oats - Ozmont (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Painter - Payne (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Peaches - Petty (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Phelps - Powell (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Preston - Quills (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Raines - Ray (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Eams - Reynolds (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Richards - Ritchie (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Roberson - Rogers (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Rose - Russell (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Sabato - Scioncalepora (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Scott - Sendia (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Sesler - Shiflett (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Skipwith - Sisk (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Skeens - Smith, G (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Smith, H - P (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Smith, R - Sparks (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Sparrow - Starkes (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Steber - Syrus (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Tabb - Taylor (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Tennant - Thompson (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Thornhill - Tolly (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Tomlinson - Tyson (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Upton - Walker (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Wallace - Warren (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Washington - Weil (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Welch - Wilkins (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Williams (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Willis - Wilson (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Wingfield - Wooten (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Word - Zimmerman (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, Correspondence, 1922-1923 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, Correspondence, 1924 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, Correspondence, 1925 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous, Correspondence, 1926 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous, Federal jurisdiction (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous, Inquiries from other states (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, Political disabilities (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous, Regain forfeited automobiles and restoration to drive, 1923-1924 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous, Regain forfeited automobiles and restoration to drive, 1925-1926 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous, Report and list of those who received conditional pardons, Copy 1 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, Report and list of those who received conditional pardons, Copy 2 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C. Prison Affairs
    - Correspondence, 1924 - 1925 Feb. (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1925 March - June (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1925 July - 1926 January (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence from Prisoners, A - H (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence from Prisoners, J - R (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence from Prisoners, S - Y (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Criminal exchange refunds (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Fines (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - State Board of Charities, Corrections, and Probations, 1922 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - State Board of Charities, Corrections, and Probations, 1923-1926 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - State Board of Public Welfare, 1924 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - State Board of Public Welfare, 1925-1926 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- Oversize, Extent: 1 cu. ft. (2 boxes). (Box Boxes 102-103)
  - Series I: Subject files, A-G. (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Series I: Subject files, H. (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Series I: Subject files, H-M. (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Series I: Subject files, O-P. (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Series I: Subject files, P-S. (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Series I: Subject files, S-T. (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Series I: Subject files, T-W. (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Series II: Extraditions, A-C. (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Series II: Extraditions, C-H. (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Series II: Extraditions, K-M. (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Series II: Extraditions, M-R. (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Series II: Extraditions, R-S. (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Series II: Extraditions, S-W. (Box 103, Folder 13)